<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nathan&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nathan&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/my-2nd-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/my-2nd-posts/</guid>
      <description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways. :zap:
Emoji Support The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.
To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site’s configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.
The Emoji cheat sheet is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.
N.B. The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotiplay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/schoolprojects/spotiplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/schoolprojects/spotiplay/</guid>
      <description>The goal of the project was to make a music playing application. In our daily life, music is with us constantly (travel, relaxation, work, parties &amp;hellip;). Nevertheless, we are used to listen to compressed music of lower quality than in the past. Indeed, the streaming platforms (predominant on this market today) are compelled to compress their audio files in order not to overload the servers and the internet connection. But some users want to listen to music in CD quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIPE : Differents image compression algorithms study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/schoolprojects/tipe-differents-image-compression-algorithms-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/schoolprojects/tipe-differents-image-compression-algorithms-study/</guid>
      <description>Personnal Project during my CPGE. A video being a series of images, studying the method used by the jpeg format to compress them would allow us to understand the fundamentals of lossy image compression, but also to see how to adapt its operation to meet new challenges.
You can appreciate here my final presentation on this project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
